♪ I'll try to be a cat ♪ (According to the Literature Reading Group author monster monster if the fire novel work "today also want to be a cat" adaptation)
=Kucingku, Pacarku=
[Episode 8]
= Episode 8 =
(Lin Yousu)
(Lin Yousu)
Miss Lin,
Nona Lin,
I've got the photo.
Aku sudah mengambil fotonya
The next step is to contact the media
Selanjutnya hubungi media untuk mempublikasikan
(Finally, it's up to you to play freely.)
♪ Terakhir tergantung padamu ♪
Okay, I know
Baik, aku tahu.
Brother Si Chen.
Kakak Si Chen.
This slap
Tamparan ini
Was returned for Pei Zhen.
Dibayar untuk Pei Zhen.
Brother Si Chen.
Kakak Si Chen.
I
Aku...
Is there any misunderstanding?
Apakah kalian ada salah paham?
Calm down.
Jangan marah, jangan marah.
You said Pei Zhen's car accident was an accident.
Kecelakaan mobil Pei Zhen adalah kecelakaan.
good
Baik.
I believe that.
Aku percaya
But when Pei Zhen was in a coma,
Tapi saat kamu koma,
Take what belongs to her.
Merebut barang milikku.
Isn't it a little unkind?
Bukankah sedikit tidak baik?
what
Apa itu?
Abominable
Sialan.
And this kind of thing.
Masih ada hal seperti ini.
I was wronged.
Aku tidak bersalah.
Are all made by my company.
Semua dilakukan oleh perusahaanku.
It has nothing to do with me.
Tidak ada hubungannya denganku.
Enough
Sudah cukup.
We are all in the same circle.
Semuanya adalah orang dalam industri yang sama.
The door is clear.
Pintunya sudah bersih.
But please remember,
Tapi ingat,
Miss Lin,
Nona Lin,
Although I'm not an expert,
Meskipun aku Fu Mou bukan orang yang sembarangan,
But I believe Fu's connections
Tapi aku percaya dengan koneksi Fu dalam industri ini,
To ban an actress like Miss Lin,
Ingin melarang aktor seperti Nona Lin
Is so easy.
Sangat mudah.
Right?
Benar tidak?
Miss Lin,
Nona Lin,
Sorry, Miss Lin.
Maaf, Nona Lin.
It's my fault to hit him.
Memukul orang adalah salahku.
But I want to say that
Tapi yang ingin aku katakan adalah
Do what you think is right, but you will have to do whatever it takes.
Jaga diri.
Pei Pei.
Pei,.
Commander Fu.
Fu Si Chen.
Wait for me.
Kamu tunggu saja.
Fu Sichen, how could you defend me?
Fu Si Chen, kamu begitu melindungi saya.
I'm so touched.
Terharu sekali.
I thought you were so handsome for the first time.
Pertama kali aku merasa kamu sangat tampan
Don't move.
Jangan bergerak.
You're not going anywhere except in my arms.
Kamu tidak boleh pergi ke mana pun selain ke pelukanku.
Brother Si Chen.
Kak Si Chen.
I brought the kitten to the office. I didn't tell you.
Aku membawa kucing ke perusahaan, tidak memberitahumu
Sorry.
Maaf ya.
Brother Si Chen.
Kak Si Chen.
You don't know how to hold her.
Aku lihat sepertinya kamu tidak terlalu bisa memeluknya.
She's not feeling well.
Dia tidak nyaman seperti ini.
Why don't I do it?
Bagaimana kalau aku saja?
You can hug?
Kamu bisa memeluk
Brother Si Chen.
Kak Si Chen.
In my opinion,
Menurutku,
This cat doesn't like you very much.
Kucing ini sepertinya tidak terlalu menyukaimu.
The twisted melons aren't sweet.
Kalau melon yang kuat ini tidak manis,
I think she likes me.
Menurutku dia lumayan menyukaiku.
Make no use of
Tidak boleh.
It stinks.
Bau sekali.
And your hair is dirty.
Bulu-bulunya juga kotor.
Take it to the shower.
Bawa pergi mandi.
Take a shower
Mandi.
No animals were harmed during the filming.
(Tidak ada hewan yang terluka saat syuting film ini)
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(Hak siar jaringan informasi serial kembali) [Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.] Eksklusif untuk menikmati)